const questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "AI tools can enhance but not replace coding skills.",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Why is hands-on experience crucial in IT learning?",
    answer: "It boosts confidence and problem-solving.",
    options: [
      "It boosts confidence and problem-solving.",
      "It replaces theoretical knowledge.",
      "It guarantees immediate job placement.",
      "It eliminates need for certificates."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "AI tools can help you generate content___.",
    answer: "faster",
    options: ["slower", "inefficiently", "faster", "manually"]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> A learner has built a basic website using HTML and CSS . They want to add interactivity and are considering learning Javascript. <br> <b> Select two correct platforms for showcasing projects.</b>`,
    answer: "Javascript cannot manipulate HTML content",
    options: [
      "Javascript support loop and functions.",
      "Javascript cannot manipulate HTML content.",
      "Javascript can interact with APIs.",
      "Javascript can handle events."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> An IT professional is preparing for job interviews and wants to enhance their online presence. They are considering different platforms to showcase their work. <br> <b> Select the best correct platforms for showcasing projects. </b> `,
    answer: "Github and Personal Website",
    options: [
      "Github and Personal Website",
      "Stack Overflow and Medium",
      "LinkedIn and Twitter",
      "GitLab and Portfolio Site"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Building real projects boosts confidence and problem-solving skills.",
    answer: "Correct",
    options: ["Correct", "Incorrect"]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the first step in starting an IT career?",
    answer: "Master the fundamentals of coding.",
    options: [
      "Master the fundamentals of coding.",
      "Build a complex website immediately.",
      "Focus on digital marketing skills.",
      "Learn advanced AI tools first."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "For interactive web pages, master javascript and___.",
    answer: "APIs",
    options: ["CSS", "APIs", "HTML", "Bootstrap"]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> A beginner is learning web developement and has mastered HTML and CSS . They are now exploring how to make their websites responsive and are considering using Bootstrap.<br> <b> Identify the incorrect Bootstrap feature for responsiveness.`,
    answer: "Bootstrap does not support grid layout.",
    options: [
      "Bootstrap does not support grid layout.",
      "Bootstrap provides responsive utilities",
      "Bootstrap includes a grid system.",
      "Bootstrap offers responsive breakpoints."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: `<b>CASE STUDY:</b> A devloper is building a porfolio to showcase their projects. They want to include both static and dynamic web pages.<br> <b> Select two correct tools for dynamic web pages.</b>`,
    answer:"APIs and Javascript",
    options: [
      "APIs and Javascript",
      "HTML and CSS",
      "APIs and HTML",
      "CSS and Javascript"
    ]
  }
];
